A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Diane Van Wie, Series 34 FA373
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Executive Chamber Staff Memos, 1962-1973; 04; 10 record cartons
  - Whitman, Ann - Drafts (A-Z), 1972 (Box 44, Folder 1200)
  - Whitman, Ann - Drafts (A-Z), 1971 (Box 44, Folder 1201)
  - Whitman, Ann - Drafts (A-Z), 1970 (Box 44, Folder 1202)
  - Wickwire, Lynn C., 1970-1971 (Box 44, Folder 1203)
  - Wiebe, Richard, 1969-1973 (Box 44, Folder 1204)
  - Wille, Frank, 1964-1969 (Box 45, Folder 1205)
  - Wilm, Harold, 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 1206)
  - Wilson, Malcolm, 1967-1973 (Box 45, Folder 1207)
  - Wilson, Malcolm, 1962-1966 (Box 45, Folder 1208)
  - Winkler, Franz E., 1970-1971 (Box 45, Folder 1209)
  - Wirth, Conrad L., 1965 (Box 45, Folder 1210)
  - Young, Fred, 1963-1966 (Box 45, Folder 1211)
  - Zaratzki, Joseph, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 1212)
- Latin American Trip, 1969-1970; 05; 1 document box(es)
  This small subseries contains material on Nelson Rockefeller's trip to Latin America in 1969. At the request of President Richard M. Nixon, Rockefeller and a team of 23 advisors visited 20 Latin American countries to solicit opinions of U.S. inter-American policies and to determine the needs and conditions of each country.
  - Mission Thank-you notes, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 1213)
  - Cannon, James, March 10-24, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 1214)
  - James Cannon File, 1969-1970 (Box 46, Folder 1215)
  - Latin America Letters, 1969-1970 (Box 46, Folder 1216)
  - Meeting for Latin American Mission Members, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 1217)
  - Thank-You notes for Mementos After Trip, 1969-1970 (Box 46, Folder 1218)
- Meetings, Luncheons, and Dinners, 1958-1973; 06; 21 document box(es)
  This subseries contains chronological files of meetings, luncheons, and dinners that Nelson Rockefeller attended or planned to attend. Types of materials include invitation lists, menus, agenda for events, correspondence, and background memos.
  - Congressional Delegation, December 22, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 1219)
  - Regents Luncheon, January 21, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 1220)
  - Cabinet Dinner, January 26, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 1221)
  - Labor Dinner, February 2, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 1222)
  - Industries Dinner, February 4, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 1223)
  - Education Dinner, February 5, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 1224)
  - Civic Group Dinner, February 6, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 1225)
  - Legislative Reception, February 10, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 1226)
  - County Chairmen Dinner, February 16, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 1227)
  - County Chairmen Dinner, February 17, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 1228)
  - County Chairmen Dinner, February 18, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 1229)
  - McHugh Report on Fallout Protection, February 18, 1960 (Box 46, Folder 1230)
  - Outdoor Exposition Dinner, February 20, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 1231)
  - Local Government Dinner, February 26, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 1232)
  - Inner Circle Dinner, March 7, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1233)
  - State University Lunch, March 12, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1234)
  - Transportation Luncheon, March 15, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1235)
  - Insurance Group Luncheon, April 9, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1236)
  - Banking Group Dinner, April 9, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1237)
  - Mansion Dinner, April 15, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1238)
  - Congressional Dinner, April 17, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1239)
  - Cabinet Dinner, April 21, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1240)
  - Mayors Dinner, April 22, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1241)
  - Dinner, Commissioners, April 29, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1242)
  - Reception, May 1, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1243)
  - State Defense Council Luncheon, July 6, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1244)
  - Buffet Supper at 810, September 23, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1245)
  - Court of Appeals Justices Dinner, October 5, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1246)
  - George Meany Dinner, October 13, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1247)
  - County Chairmen Dinner, October 15, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1248)
  - County Chairmen Dinner, October 16, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1249)
  - County Chairmen Dinner, October 23, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1250)
  - County Chairmen Dinner, October 27, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1251)
  - Reception for Dr. Victor Belaunde - 810, November 6, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1252)
  - Rhode Island Republican State Committee, November 20, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1253)
  - White Sulphur Springs Trip, December 2, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1254)
  - Women's Civil Defense Seminar, December 3, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1255)
  - New York Bible Society, December 4, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1256)
  - Conference for Legislative Leaders, December 7, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1257)
  - Federal Reserve Bank Luncheon, December 9, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1258)
  - Jane Todd Testimonial Dinner, December 9, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1259)
  - Pre-Legislative Leaders Breakfast, December 21, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1260)
  - New York State Conference of Farm Organizations, December 28, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1261)
  - Informal Reception for Legislators, January 6, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 1262)
  - Pre-Legislative Leaders Breakfast, January 11, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 1263)
  - Legislative Reception, January 11, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 1264)
  - Buffet Supper for Cabinet Members, January 11, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 1265)
  - Legislators Informal Dinner, January 12, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 1266)
  - New York State Women's Joint Legislative Forum, January 12, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 1267)
  - New York State Agricultural Society, January 13, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 1268)
  - Pre-Legislative Leaders Breakfast, January 18, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 1269)
  - Republican Senators and Assemblymen Informal Dinner, January 19, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 1270)
  - Vice Chairmen Luncheons, January 19 and 26, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 1271)
  - Republican Senators and Assemblymen Informal Dinner, January 20, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 1272)
  - New York State Insurance Department Centennial Dinner, January 21, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 1273)
  - White House Conference on Fallout Protection, January 24, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 1274)
  - Pre-Legislative Leaders Supper, January 25, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 1275)
  - Republican Senators and Assemblymen Informal Dinner, January 26, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 1276)
  - Dinner for Ike, January 27, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 1277)
  - Budget Luncheon, January 28, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1278)
  - Budget Meeting 1/4 With Republican Legislators, February 1, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1279)
  - Empire State Chamber of Commerce Annual Legislative Dinner, February 2, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1280)
  - New York State Republican Chairman and Chairmen Luncheon, February 3, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1281)
  - New York State County Chairman and Vice Chairmen Luncheon, February 3, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1282)
  - Luncheon Brandeis University, Boston, Massachusetts, February 7, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1283)
  - College Presidents Luncheon, February 8, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1284)
  - Pre-Legislative Leaders Breakfast, February 9, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1285)
  - New York State Association of Towns, New York City, February 9, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1286)
  - Erie County Republican Dinner, February 10, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1287)
  - American Association of School Administrators, Atlantic City, February 14, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1288)
  - Pre-Legislative Leaders Breakfast, February 15, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1289)
  - League of Women Voters of New York, Legislative Conference, February 15, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1290)
  - Publishers Meeting, February 17, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1291)
  - Union Leaders Dinner, New York City, February 17, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1292)
  - Pre-Legislative Leaders Breakfast, February 22, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1293)
  - State Defense Council Meeting, February 23, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1294)
  - American Legion Dinner, February 23, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1295)
  - Associated Industries Luncheon, February 24, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1296)
  - Pre-Legislative Leaders Breakfast, February 29, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1297)
  - New York State Federation of Women's Republican Clubs, March 1, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1298)
  - New York State Association of Broadcasters Legislative Dinner, March 1, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1299)
  - Board of Regents Luncheon, March 2, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1300)
  - New York Congressional Delegation Dinner, March 2, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1301)
  - Civil Defense Seminar, March 4, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1302)
  - Pre-Legislative Leaders Breakfast, March 7, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1303)
  - Civil Service Employees Association, March 10, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1304)
  - Newspaper People at Discussion of Recreation Facilities, March 11, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1305)
  - Legislative Correspondents Association Dinner, March 12, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1306)
  - Advisory Council for the Advancement of Industrial Research Luncheon, March 14, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1307)
  - Meeting, Newburgh-Beacon Bridge, March 15, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1308)
  - Kick-Off for the United Jewish Appeal Campaign, March 16, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1309)
  - Boy Scout Breakfast, March 18, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1310)
  - Pre-Legislative Leaders Meeting, March 20, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1311)
  - Pre-Legislative Leaders Meeting, March 27, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1312)
  - Chautauqua County Republican Committee Dinner, April 7, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1313)
  - New York State University College Groundbreaking, April 8, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1314)
  - Pan American Day World Affairs Council at Rochester, April 13, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1315)
  - Groundbreaking Di-Noc Chemical Arts Inc., April 13, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1316)
  - Groundbreaking Kordite Corporation, April 13, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1317)
  - Fulton County Community Development Corp. Dinner, April 14, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1318)
  - Third Seder Passover Celebration - National Committee for Labor Israel, April 16, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1319)
  - Schneebeli Campaign Luncheon, April 20, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1320)
  - Schneebeli Campaign Tea, April 20, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1321)
  - Schneebeli Campaign Dinner, April 20, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1322)
  - Women's Council Department of Commerce Luncheon, April 21, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1323)
  - World Affairs Council Luncheon, April 22, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1324)
  - Convocation Address, University of Chicago Law Center, May 1, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1325)
  - Lincoln Square Cornerstone Ceremony, May 3, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1326)
  - Governor's Conference on Automation, June 1-3, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1327)
  - Rally for United States Senate Committee, North Dakota, June 3, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1328)
  - Rally - Stutzman County Republican Committee and Jamestown Chamber of Commerce, June 4, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1329)
  - Rally - Bismarck Republican Committee, North Dakota, June 4, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1330)
  - New York State Lions Convention, June 6, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1331)
  - "Preview of Local Government", 1960-70, June 7, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1332)
  - Memorial Service for NAR's Father, June 8, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1333)
  - Annual Parade of Brooklyn Sunday School Union, June 9, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1334)
  - British Exhibition, June 10, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1335)
  - Luncheon for the New York State Republican Committee, June 14, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1336)
  - Twelfth Annual Dinner of New York State Republican Committee, June 14, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1337)
  - Binghamton Rotary Club Luncheon, June 21, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1338)
  - Committee for Celebration of 75th Anniversary of State Forest Preserve, June 22, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1339)
  - Meeting of Governors Conference - Montana, June 29, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1340)
  - Private Luncheon, New York City, July 6, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1341)
  - Dinner for the New York Delegation, Chicago, July 24, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1342)
  - United Republican Financial Committee (URFC) Dinner, September 12, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 1343)
  - Los Angeles Town Hall Luncheon, September 15, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 1344)
  - Joseph W. Martin Testimonial Dinner - Taunton, Massachusetts, September 18, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 1345)
  - Meeting of Committee on White House Conference On Aging - Albany, September 19, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 1346)
  - Ontario City Women's Republican Clubs Dinner, Geneva, New York, October 10, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 1347)
  - Steuben City Republican Committee Luncheon, Corning, New York, October 10, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 1348)
  - Chemung City Republican Committee Breakfast, Elmira, New York ?, October 11, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 1349)
  - Upstate New York Campaign, October 14, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 1350)
  - Luncheon for King and Queen of Denmark, October 16, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 1351)
  - Visit of King and Queen of Denmark, October 16, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 1352)
  - Citizens for Nixon-Lodge Rally, New York City, October 23, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 1353)
  - Heald Committee Meeting, November 14, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 1354)
  - Student Conference on United States Affairs, West Point, November 30, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 1355)
  - Electoral College Reception, December 19, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 1356)
  - Cabinet Dinner and Cocktails, January 9, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1357)
  - Legislators' Reception, January 9, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1358)
  - Chairmen and Vice Chairmen, January 10, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1359)
  - New York State Women's Joint Legislative Forum, January 10, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1360)
  - New York State Citizens Council on Traffic Safety, January 16, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1361)
  - County Chairmen and Vice Chairmen Luncheon, January 17, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1362)
  - Annual Farm Dinner, January 18, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1363)
  - Building Trades Employer's Association Dinner, January 19, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1364)
  - Opening of Harman-Kardon Plant, January 19, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1365)
  - Regents Luncheon, January 23, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1366)
  - Dinner for Republican Legislators, January 24, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1367)
  - New York State Association of Agricultural Fair Societies, January 24, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1368)
  - Associated Industries Luncheon, January 25, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1369)
  - Dinner for Republican Legislators, January 25, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1370)
  - New York State Highway Superintendents Association Meeting, January 26, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1371)
  - Budget Luncheon, January 26, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1372)
  - Women's National Republican Club Luncheon, January 28, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1373)
  - Dinner for Deputy Industrial Commissioner Julius Loos, January 30, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1374)
  - Dinner for Republican Legislators, January 31, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1375)
  - Meeting on Lincoln Center, February 3, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1376)
  - Meeting with Representatives of New York State Council of Churches, February 6, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1377)
  - New York State Council of Churches Legislative Branch, February 7, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1378)
  - Annual Meeting of Association of Towns of New York State, February 7, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1379)
  - Niagara Falls Chamber of Commerce Dinner, February 9, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1380)
  - Legislative Reception, February 14, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1381)
  - Legislative Reception, February 16, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1382)
  - Luncheon, American Meat Institute, February 20, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1383)
  - Dinner, Officers and Directors of New York State Publishers Association, February 20, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1384)
  - Railroad Luncheon, February 21, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1385)
  - Annual Legislative Meeting of New York Farm Bureau, February 28, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1386)
  - Dinner, Civil Service Employees Association, March 2, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1387)
  - Inner Circle Dinner, March 4, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1388)
  - Legislative Dinner New York Association of Radio and Television Broadcasting, March 7, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1389)
  - Businessman's Dinner, March 10, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1390)
  - New York State Army National Guard, March 14, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1391)
  - Board of Regents Dinner, March 23, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1392)
  - Private Dinner, April 6, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1393)
  - Annual Dinner, Suffolk County Republican Committee, April 13, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1394)
  - Middle Atlantic Grange Lecturers' Conference, April 14, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1395)
  - Private Dinner, April 21, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1396)
  - New York State Intercollegiate Mock Senate, April 22, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1397)
  - Cocktails and Dinner for Governors in Washington, D. C., May 8, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1398)
  - Luncheon Board of Trustees of State University, May 18, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1399)
  - State University Board of Trustees Luncheon, May 18, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1400)
  - Groundbreaking Ceremonies of Atlantic Cement Company Ravena, May 19, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1401)
  - Dinner Sponsored by United Young Republican Club, May 19, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1402)
  - Boscobel Restoration, May 20, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1403)
  - Dinner - Steering Committee of New York State Congressional Delegation, Washington, D. C., May 21, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1404)
  - Luncheon for Bank Heads, May 25, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1405)
  - Commerce and Industry Association Cocktail Party, May 25, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1406)
  - Dedication of Hortense B. Sterns Apartments, May 26, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1407)
  - Testimonial Dinner, June 1, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1408)
  - Luncheon for Republican State Committee, June 8, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1409)
  - Dedication of International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU) Workmen's Circle Home of Aged, June 11, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1410)
  - Local Government Workshop, June 12, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1411)
  - Meeting with Leaders of Puerto Rican Community, June 22, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1412)
  - Private Dinner, July 5, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1413)
  - Harpur College, July 13, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1414)
  - Meeting with President of Pakistan, July 14, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1415)
  - 43rd National Convention of American Legion, July 27, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1416)
  - Groundbreaking Youth Division Camp, July 27, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1417)
  - Informal Dinner, Private, July 31, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1418)
  - Benevolent and Protective Order of the Elks (BPOE), August 21, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1419)
  - Monroe County Fair, August 22, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1420)
  - Convention, Firemen's Association of the State of New York, August 22, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1421)
  - Convention, Italian-American War Veterans of the United States, August 25, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1422)
  - Convention, Zionist Organization of American, September 2, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1423)
  - Dinner, Syracuse Chamber of Commerce, September 5, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1424)
  - Private Luncheon, September 28, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1425)
  - Ceremonies, Induction of Units of New York Air National Guard, October 1, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1426)
  - Private Dinner, October 11, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1427)
  - Civil Defense Council Meeting Lunch, October 16, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1428)
  - Governor's Reception, October 18, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1429)
  - Republican Dinner, October 24, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1430)
  - Onondaga County Republican Fund Raising Dinner, October 30, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1431)
  - South Shore Lanes Bowling Alley Appearance, November 1, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1432)
  - Columbia Association in Civil Service, November 5, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1433)
  - Labor Leaders Meeting, Dinner, December 26, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1434)
  - Occupation Safety Luncheon, December 26, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1435)
  - Political Meeting All Day, December 27, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1436)
  - Dinner for British Jurists, January 9, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1437)
  - New York State Women's Joint Legislative Forum, January 9, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1438)
  - Governor's Conference on Occupational Safety, January 11, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1439)
  - Luncheon with Directors of Associated Press, January 17, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1440)
  - Dinner for Republican Legislators, January 17, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1441)
  - 1962 Campaign, Heads of Special Committees List (Box 52, Folder 1442)
  - Dedication of Albright-Knox Art Gallery, January 19, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1443)
  - Luncheon Meeting of General Managers of General Electric's New York Operation, January 22, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1444)
  - Breakfast for Republican Legislators, January 23, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1445)
  - Meeting on Youth and Work, January 23, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1446)
  - Westchester Republican County Committee Dinner, January 25, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1447)
  - Editor's Seminar, January 28, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1448)
  - Meeting of New York State Society of Newspaper Editors, January 29, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1449)
  - Greeting New York State Nurses' Association, January 29, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1450)
  - Luncheon for County Chairmen and Vice Chairmen, January 29, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1451)
  - Luncheon for County Chairmen and Vice Chairmen, January 30, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1452)
  - Breakfast for Republican Legislators, January 31, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1453)
  - Luncheon for County Chairmen and Vice Chairmen, February 5, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1454)
  - Godkin Lecture, February 7, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1455)
  - Godkin Lecture II, February 8, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1456)
  - Godkin Lecture III, February 9, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1457)
  - Meeting with Business and Professional Women's Clubs, February 12, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1458)
  - Meeting with New York State Council of Churches, February 12, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1459)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars Legislative Dinner, February 13, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1460)
  - "Report Ceremony", Region 2, Boy Scouts of America, February 13, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1461)
  - Rural Citizens Breakfast, February 14, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1462)
  - Republican Aviation Plant Meeting, February 16, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1463)
  - Luncheon for Council on the Arts, February 17, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1464)
  - Rome, Utica Tour, Itinerary, February 21-23, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1465)
  - Legislative Reception, February 27, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1466)
  - John Glenn Reception, March 1, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1467)
  - Inner Circle Dinner, March 10, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1468)
  - Dinner for Legislative Wives, March 17, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1469)
  - State University Board of Trustees Luncheon, March 19, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1470)
  - Luncheon for Board of Regents, March 22, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1471)
  - Luncheon of Finance and Advisory Committee of New York Citizens Council on Traffic Safety, March 23, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1472)
  - Upstate New York Republican Finance Committee Luncheon, March 27, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1473)
  - Dedication Ceremony Young Israel of Concorse, March 28, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1474)
  - "Salute to Javits" Dinner, April 7, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1475)
  - Dinner in Honor of Consul General Slingenburg, April 8, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1476)
  - Luncheon Session of Symposium on "Jobs for Women", April 10, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1477)
  - Dinner for Counsel's Staff, April 13, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1478)
  - Luncheon of the Board of Trustees of Cornell University, April 14, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1479)
  - Alpha Zeta Fraternity Dinner, April 14, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1480)
  - Detroit Trip Schedule, April 15-16, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1481)
  - Economic Club of Detroit Luncheon, April 16, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1482)
  - Washington, D. C. Trip Schedule, April 16-18, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1483)
  - Dinner for Republican Members of New York State Congressional Delegation, April 17, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1484)
  - Dinner for Regional Planners, April 18, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1485)
  - Albany Institute of History and Art's Advisory Board Meeting, April 18, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1486)
  - Temporary State Commission on Capital City Luncheon, April 24, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1487)
  - Chautauqua-Cattaraugus Tour, May 3, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1488)
  - Chautauqua-Cattaraugus Tour, May 4-5, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1489)
  - "Rockefeller Day" 8th Empire State Labor Management Exhibition, May 5, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1490)
  - Wyoming Trip, May 11-12, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1491)